# **JOSEPH GOUGH**

765 My Siteel, Detroit, MI 10987 j.gough@etnail.com (123) 456-7890

Seasoned and talented sales director with 8+ years' experience in the technology industry. Adept at inspiring and motivating sales teams to achieve and exceed ambitious revenue goals. Capable of thinking critically and generating creative solutions to problems under pressure. Outstanding track record of identifying emerging areas for growth and capitalizing on sales opportunities.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Science in Marketing**

University Of Michigan, Dearborn. Mi September 2006- June 2010

#### Master of Science in Business Administration

Eastern Michigan University, Ypsilanti, Mi September 201**0-** June 2012

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- · Training and mentorship
- Positive and assertive leadership style
- Analytical thinking and strategic planning
- In-depth technology industry knowledge

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

• Certified Professional Sales Leader, ^gp 2014

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### TECHNOLOGY SALES DIRECTOR

Accenture, Detroit. MI March 2014 - Present

- Identify areas for growth, set strategic progress plans, and generate short- and long-term team sales targets
- Manage over 100+ sales representatives, monitoring performance and providing ongoing mentorship and support
- Perform new recruit training and orientation and lead professional development sessions
- Liaise with 12 major corporate clients to gain detailed insights into their organization's targets and problems and propose suitable products and services

## TECHNOLOGY SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Tempo Technologies. Detroit. MI July 2012-March 2014

- Actively sourced and followed up potential leads and maintained long-term relationships with existing clients
- Managed the entire sales cycle from lead sourcing to completion
- Worked collaboratively with colleagues to achieve demanding targets to tight deadlines
- Planned and managed promotional events and product demonstrations to build brand engagement and prospect for new clients